=Afterlife of Love and Revenge= =Episode 10=
= الآخرة من الحب والانتقام = = الحلقة 10 =
(Zhao Qianjin)
(تشاو تشيانجين)
Ridiculous!
سخيف!
I'll surely step up for you!
أنا بالتأكيد سأصعد من أجلك!
Qianjin.
تشيانجين.
I don't want you to step up for me.
لا أريدك أن تتقدم لي.
I...
أنا...
I want to marry Pang Longyue.
أريد الزواج من Pang Longyue.
Was your brain damaged after getting hit by her?
هل تضرر دماغك بعد أن صدمتها؟
She's famous for being an infamous woman.
إنها مشهورة بكونها امرأة سيئة السمعة.
I wouldn't want her if she's not.
لا أريدها إذا لم تكن كذلك.
If I've married her,
إذا تزوجتها ،
I can do whatever I want in Qingshui County.
يمكنني أن أفعل ما أريد في مقاطعة Qingshui.
You're smart.
انت ذكي.
Just go grab her if you want to marry her.
فقط اذهب وجذبها إذا كنت تريد الزواج منها.
Let's go!
لنذهب!
Miss Longyue.
ملكة جمال Longyue.
Looking at all these,
بالنظر إلى كل هذا ،
are you going to tell me that you like me?
هل ستخبرني أنك معجب بي؟
So what if I like you?
اذا ماذا لو كنت معجب بك؟
I'm also going to marry you.
أنا أيضا سوف أتزوجك.
Right?
حق؟
Yes, marry him!
نعم تزوجه!
If you're smart,
إذا كنت ذكيًا ،
just obey and follow me home.
فقط أطعني واتبعني إلى المنزل.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
I'll burn your medicine stall.
سأحرق كشك الأدوية الخاص بك.
Let me be frank.
اسمحوا لي أن أكون صريحا.
Li Qingmu
لي تشينغمو
wants to divorce me.
يريد أن يطلقني.
I can't live with him anymore.
لا أستطيع العيش معه بعد الآن.
They're too poor.
إنهم فقراء جدا.
It seems like
انها تبدو مثل
marrying you is not a bad choice.
الزواج منك ليس خيارا سيئا.
Really? Let's get on the litter.
هل حقا؟  هيا بنا على القمامة.
Don't rush it.
لا تتعجل.
Give me back the medicine first.
أعطني الدواء أولاً.
Also, I have one request.
أيضا ، لدي طلب واحد.
You
أنت
will go to Miss Longyue's place
سيذهب إلى مكان الآنسة لونجيو
and send back all the medicine.
ونعيد كل الأدوية.
Okay.
تمام.
Miss Longyue,
ملكة جمال لونجيو ،
tell me what you need.
اخبرني ماذا تريد.
Okay.
تمام.
Use the litter to carry me
استخدم القمامة لتحملني
for two rounds in the market.
لجولتين في السوق.
Also, you have to tell others that you like me.
أيضًا ، عليك أن تخبر الآخرين أنك معجب بي.
After all, we just had a fight.
بعد كل شيء ، لقد تشاجرنا للتو.
I don't want them to gossip about
لا أريدهم أن يثرثروا
how I force you to marry me.
كيف أجبرني على الزواج مني.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll go back and get changed into my wedding dress.
سأعود وأغير فستان زفافي.
Ladies and gentlemen,
سيداتي وسادتي،
we're gathered here today
اجتمعنا هنا اليوم
because I, Zhao Baidou, am getting married!
لأنني ، تشاو بايدو ، سأتزوج!
My bride
عروستي
is someone unexpected by everyone.
هو شخص غير متوقع من قبل الجميع.
But, please believe me that
لكن ، من فضلك صدقني ذلك
she didn't force me.
لم تجبرني.
I did it of my own will.
لقد فعلت ذلك من إرادتي.
I really like her.
أنا حقا أحبها.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
He's a man.
إنه رجل.
It's not him that I'm marrying.
أنا لست متزوجًا.
How can he marry a man?
كيف يتزوج رجل؟
Did you say you really like him?
هل قلت أنك معجب به حقًا؟
I didn't know that the bully in Qingshui County
لم أكن أعرف أن الفتوة في مقاطعة Qingshui
has this kind of hobby.
لديه هذا النوع من الهوايات.
I...
أنا...
Here's your medicine.
هذا هو دوائك.
I can't collect protection fee
لا يمكنني تحصيل رسوم الحماية
in this street anymore.
في هذا الشارع بعد الآن.
You're useless!
أنت عديم الفائدة!
Qianjin,
تشيانجين ،
do you have any idea how we can punish them?
هل لديك فكرة كيف يمكننا معاقبتهم؟
I don't,
أنا لا،
but she does.
لكنها تفعل.
Who is that?
من ذاك؟
Just do what I say
فقط افعل ما اقول
and
و
she'll be chased out of Li family
سيتم طردها من عائلة لي
tomorrow.
الغد.
♪You're the fated love coming from the immortal world♪
أنت الحب المقدّر الآتي من العالم الخالد
♪You tie the red strings on the tips of my fingers♪
♪ تقوم بربط الخيوط الحمراء على أطراف أصابعي ♪
♪My heart won't change even if time passes♪
♪ قلبي لن يتغير حتى لو مر الوقت
♪I'll wait for the love in the old place as promised♪
♪ سأنتظر الحب في المكان القديم كما وعدت ♪